manh.com 2018-12-20

# Manhattan Associates' Privacy Policy | Manhattan Associates

Effective Date: May 14, 2015

## Introduction

Manhattan Associates, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “Manhattan Associates”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website manh.com (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * on this Website.
  * in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, or
  * any third party.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

## Manhattan Associates’ Collection of Information

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“personal information”). Manhattan Associates will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide it to us.
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.

The information you provide us may include:

  * information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering on our Website or requesting information through our Website. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * your search queries on the Website.

Information we collect automatically may include:

  * details of your visits to our Website, including communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

## Manhattan Associates’ Use of Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * to present our Website and its contents to you in the most effective manner for you and your computer or mobile device
  * to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * to contact you with offers of goods and services or information that may be of interest to you about supply chain sector services, materials, news or training.
  * to allow you to access limited-entry areas of our website as may be appropriate.
  * to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services.
  * in any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * for any other purpose with your consent.

If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please do not provide us with your information.

## Sharing of Information and International Transfers

For marketing purposes, we may share your information with our business partners, or we may send you information about those partners’ goods and services. We or our business partners may contact you by mail, telephone, fax, email or other electronic messaging service with offers of goods and services or information that may be of interest to you about supply chain sector services, materials, news or training. By providing us with your fax number, telephone numbers, email or mailing address you consent to being contacted by these methods for these purposes. If you do not wish to receive such information from us or our business partners, please contact us using the details provided below any time. No further action is necessary if you have previously indicated to us that you do not want to receive such marketing material.

Because Manhattan Associates is a global company, your personal information may be shared with other Manhattan Associates business units around the world. They will protect your personal information in accordance with this Manhattan Associates Privacy Policy.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business[ and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them].
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Manhattan Associates’ assets, in which personal information held by Manhattan Assocaites about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [terms of use](http://www.manh.com/terms-of-use) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

## Cookies and Other Technology

The information we collect automatically helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

## Links to Other Websites

Our Website may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by companies not owned by Manhattan Associates. These other sites or linked third-party sites may have their own privacy notices, which you should review if you visit those sites. We are not responsible for the content of any sites not owned by Manhattan Associates, any use of those sites, or those sites’ privacy practices.

## How We Protect Personal Information

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

## Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not register on the Website. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, we will delete that information.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

If your personal details change, if you change your mind about any of your marketing preferences or if you have any queries about how we use your information, please let us know by calling us at +1 770.955.7070, or by emailing us at [dataprotection@manh.com](mailto:dataprotection@manh.com).
